

## DHIRAJ KUMAR

Extremely motivated to constantly develop my technical skills and grow professionally .And to work in a firm with a professional work driven environment where my skills and knowledge will have valuable application in the growth of the organization.

### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

BATCH - ( OCTOBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021)

### **BIM CERTIFICATION, TechnoStruct Academy**

Certification in BIM, with specialization in Architecture, MEP, Structure.

Primary Codes knowledge: USA

Secondary Codes knowledge: UK & India

BATCH - (JULY 2015 - JUNE 2019)

Gandhi Institute for Technological advancement, BBSR, ODISHA

B.tech (Civil engineering)

8.0 CGPA

BATCH - (APRIL 2013 - MAY 2015)

Dav public school, Hazaribagh

Intermediate

79.5%

BATCH - (2013)

Day public school, Hazaribagh

Matriculation

9.4 CGPA

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

August 2021- Present: Working on Residential Projects(Freelancing)

As Architect, Planning & Site engineering

Software included: Autocad, Revit, Staad Pro, Ms Excel,

Enscape.

**Technostruct Academy, Hyderabad** 

Oct 2020- JAN 2021 (Intern BIM Engineer )

California-based complex project called Aero Apartments.

June 2019 - July 2021 : M/s Anand Kumar Singhania

As Site & Planning engineer

Working for NTPC extension project at Barauni, Bihar.

Site including areas of Coal handling plant.



# DHIRAJ KUMAR

## **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

♣ Revit Architecture, Structure & MEP

4 Autocad (2D &3D) & MEP

Staad Pro

Point cloud Modelling

**♣** BIM 360

Navisworks

Enscape

Dynamo

4 3Ds Max

MS-Office

# **HIGHLIGHTS**

Experienced in Site Execution & Planning

Proficient with my software skills

## **LANGUAGES**

4 English

4 Hindi

# **PERSONAL DETAILS**

♣ Date of Birth:	29 /05/1996
♣ Sex:	Male
Nationality:	Indian
Current Address:	Boreya, Ranchi, Jharkhand, 834006
Permanent Address:	Mandai Khurd, Hazaribagh, Jharkhand, 825301
	7519792384, 7504131275
🖶 Email:	esdhir49@gmail.com
♣ LinkedIn:	https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhiraj -kumar-b5a159160